Guide to the Cornell University Centennial Celebration Records, 1957-1967, 1960-1965 (bulk)
Cornell University Centennial Celebration Records, 1957-1967, 1960-1965 (bulk)
- Series IV: Cornell Centennial Planning Committee
  - Space Needs of the University (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - New Tools to Probe the Atom and Outer Space (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - New Tasks for the Graduate School of Education (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - The Cornell Faculty: Key to Excellence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Avalon Foundation, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Research: A Tool for Better Teaching, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Space Needs of the University (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New Tools to Probe the Atom and Outer Space (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New Tasks for the Graduate School of Education (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Drafts (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Drafts-continued (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Advance gift brochure (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Centennial brochure, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Teaching Fellowships (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Photo Exhibit (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cornell's Next Hundred Years, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Citations, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Molecular Biology, 1961-62 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Physical Sciences (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Preliminary Statement (insiders' statement), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Preliminary Statement (insiders' statement), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General Photography (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Position Papers Order Card, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Materials Science Center, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Willard Straight Hall, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Nuclear Reactor, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Law (special presentation), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence concerning photography, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Trustees preliminary statement (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Giving Securities to Cornell (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Tax Piece, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Subscription Card (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous brochures (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Series V. President's Office
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Celebration Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Campaign material, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Campaign material, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Campaign material, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Campaign material, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Campaign material, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Social Science Sub-Committee; Home Economics, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Centennial: A Preliminary Statement on Problems of University Development, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Centennial Planning Committees, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Centennial Planning Committees, 1957-1961 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Centennial Planning Committees, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Kersting, Brown and Company Reports, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Kersting, Brown and Company Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - "The Next Ten to Twenty Years in Engineering", 1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Centennial Campaign Interim Reports, July 21, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Centennial Campaign-Suggestions for Local Chairmen and Committeemen, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - A Confidential Assessment of Cornell's Immediate Needs and Opportunities on Behalf of Its Centennial Program, September 30, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Trustees Preliminary Statement (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Cornell University Centennial Campaign: Dinner, September 27, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Preliminary Statement, November 15, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Cornell University Centennial Campaign: Luncheons, September 27-28, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, September 8, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Centennial Planning Committee; Sub-Committee for the Social Sciences, December, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Centennial Planning Committee; State College of Home Economics, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Centennial Planning Committee; Social Sciences, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Centennial Planning Committee: The School of Education, February, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - N.Y.S. School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Social Science Research Center at Cornell University, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Center for International Studies, October 24, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Draft of proposal to National Institutes of Health, May 6, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Student Affairs, 1960-1964 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - School of Education, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - School of Agriculture, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Admission of the Undergraduate, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Law School, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Business and Public Administration, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education Department, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Research at Cornell, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Biological Sciences, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Physical Sciences, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - College of Engineering, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Newsclippings (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Development of Cornell University Libraries, 1955-1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - School of Education, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Minutes-Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Admission of the Undergraduate Academic Advising in the University, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "The Future Size of the University", December 7, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Biology, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Two Proposals for Strengthening the Humanities at Cornell", October 31, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Compensation and Benefits Projected Immediate Increases, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Business and Public Administration, Home Economics and Hotel Administration, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - International Interests of Cornell University, March 22, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Problems of University Development, January 8, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Law School, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - College of Architecture: The Arts and Their Practices, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Dean's Statement-Graduate School-Background Memo, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Statement from Dale R. Corson, Dean of the Engineering School, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Position and Working Papers-Dean's Papers, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sub-committees; biological physical sciences, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Sub-committees; biological physical sciences, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Sub-committees; humanities social sciences, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Sub-committees; humanities social sciences, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Centennial Planning Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - "Cornell in Sound And Light"-corrected script, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - "Cornell in Sound And Light"-corrected script, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - "Cornell in Sound and Light", 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - "Cornell in Sound and Light" correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Series VI. Tape Recordings
  - Alama Mater and Evening Star, Glee Club (original), June 19, 1965; tr. 4827
  - Alma Mater (1st edition, Bishop), June 19, 1965; tr. 4828
  - Final Tape used for Sound and Light Program, June 19, 1965; tr. 4829
  - Bishop original, June 19, 1965; tr.4830
  - Miscellaneous New York Cast, June 19, 1965; tr.4831
  - Master #1, Background Music, June 19, 1965; tr. 4832
  - Master #2, June 19, 1965; tr. 4833
  - Dureyea Part I, Master Copy, June 19, 1965; tr.4834
  - Dureyea Part II, Master Copy, June 19, 1965; tr. 4835
  - Narration-no cuts, June 19, 1965; tr.4836b
  - Music Equalized, June 19, 1965; tr. 4837b
  - Music Edited, June 19, 1965; tr. 4838b
  - Son Et Lumière-complete program with music mix, June 19, 1965; tr.4839b
  - Sound and Light, Master Copy, June 19, 1965; tr. 4840
  - Karel Husa, Festive Ode, October 9, 1964; tr. 4841
  - Ives Seminar #1, June 18, 1965; tr. 4842
  - Ives Seminar #2, June 18, 1965; tr. 4843
  - Statler Seminar #1 (students), June 17, 1965; tr. 4844
  - Statler Seminar #2 (students), June 17, 1965; tr. 4845
  - Statler Seminar #1, June 18, 1965; tr. 4846
  - Statler Seminar #2, June 18, 1965; tr. 4847
  - Adlai Stevenson at Convocation Banquet, October 9, 1964; tr. 4848
  - Address by Sir Eric Ashby, Cornell Centennial Convocation, #1, October 9, 1964; tr. 4849
  - Address by Sir Eric Ashby, #2, October 9, 1964; tr. 4850
  - Mackesey Talk I, no date; tr. 4851
  - Mackesey Talk II, no date; tr. 4852
  - Morris Bishop Convocation Charter Day, April 27, 1965; tr. 4853
  - Mackesey Talk, no date; tr. 4854
  - Unidentified, no date; tr. 4855, 4856
  - Arthur Dean Dinner, Nos. 1, 2, April 15, 1966; tr. 4857, 4858
  - Auditions for "Cornell in Sound and Light", no date; tr. 4859
  - Barton Convocation, Nos. 1-3, April 27, 1965; tr. 4860-4862
  - Olin Seminar, Nos. 1-4, April 28, 1965; tr. 4863-4866
  - Olin Seminar, Nos. 1-4, April 29, 1965; tr. 4867-4870
  - Olin Seminar, Nos. 1-4, April 30, 1965; tr. 4871-4874
  - Statler Ballrom Dinner, Nos. 1, 2, April 30, 1965; tr. 4875, 4876
  - Statler Ballroom Luncheon Complete Remarks (original), April 27, 1965; tr. 4877
  - Statler Symposium, Nos. 1-5, Peter Medawar, speaker, April 28, 1965; tr. 4878-4882
  - Statler Symposium, Nos. 1-5, Panel discussion on social sciences, April 29, 1965; tr. 4883-4887
  - Statler Symposium, Nos. 1-5, April 30, 1965; tr. 4888-4892
  - Statler Symposium, Nos. 1-4, May 1, 1965; tr. 4893-4896
  - Son et Lumière "Cornell in Sound and Light", no date; tr. 4897
  - Unidentified, no date; tr. 4898
- Series VII. Collection #47-4-1474
  - Three boxes of additional material. (Box 47-4-1474 - 1-3)
  - Centennial Reports from Each School, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 1)
    Agriculture
    Architecture
    Arts and Sciences
    Business and Public Administration
    Education
    Graduate
    Home Economics
    Hotel Administration
    ILR
    Law
    Nutrition
    Veterinary Medicine
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 1, Folder 1)
    Academic Advising in the University
    Admission of the Undergraduate to the University
    Honors Work at Cornell
    Report on Student Housing
    A Long Look at the Cornell University Graduate School
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 1, Folder 2)
    Report of the Committee on Long Range Planning to the Centennial Planning Committee
    Faculty Compensation and Benefits
    International Interests of Cornell University
    Medical Services at Cornell
    Department of Physical Education and Athletics
    Non-Curricular Programs of the University
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 1, Folder 3)
    Educational Opportunities in the Freshman Year
    The Responsibilities and Functions of Cornell United Religious Works
    Cornell University Libraries
    Student Union
    Graduate Majors and Minors by Fields of Instruction
    Office of the Registrar
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 2, Folder 1)
    Harold Seymour Report
    Space Needs of the College of Arts and Sciences
    Revised Outline Plan for CU Centennial Campaign
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 2, Folder 2)
    The Arts
    Minutes
    Budgets
    Progress Reports
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 2)
    August Minutes
    Finance
    Preliminary Statement
    November Minutes
    Report to Board of Trustees
    June Minutes
    March Minutes
    December Minutes
    Art Museum
    The Future Size of the University Report
    Sciences
    Subcommittees
  - Natural Sciences, 1960 (Box 47-4-1474 - 3, Folder 1)
  - Humanities, 1961 (Box 47-4-1474 - 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 47-4-1474 - 3)
    Faculty Committee on Long-Range Planning
    Outlines
    Position Papers
    Report on Centers
    Committee on Calender Revisions
    Library Space Predictions
- Series VIII. Memorabilia
  - Six wine glasses produced by the Owens-Illinois Glass Company, Ohio at the request of Preston Levis '24. The mold was destroyed by request, after only one use. (Box 14)